followlike.net 2018-08-12

# FollowLike - Social Exchange Community

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which FollowLike collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [FollowLike](http://www.followlike.net/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by FollowLike.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.   
Users will be asked for email and country upon registration and followlike will collect IP address, browser infomation and device type upon Registration or Log in, to aid in delivering our service to you. We will collect further personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us, in their account settings which can be edited and or deleted at any time by the user. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. Users have to Enable (Allow) Cookies upon first viewing our site. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. If you delete your Cookies you will be re-asked by the site to Enable Cookies if you wish

**How we use collected information**

FollowLike may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To process payments_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _\- To send periodic emails (Opt-In Only)_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site or disabling this option in their settings.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Requesting your held personal information**

If you ever wish to know what information we hold about you, in full or part, you can contact us by either internal support ticket or from your registered email, asking for a list of what we have on record.

**Deleting ALL your held personal information (Right to be forgotten)**

If you ever wish to have your information cleared / wiped from our system, there are two ways.   
1) Simply login and delete your account in account settings. This will put your account on the purge list to be stripped (wiped from our system) with all your information.   
2) Send us a Delete request via email from your registered email asking for an account deletion. This is permanant and does not allow you a chance to cancel the request, which you get if you manually delete your account and information. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

FollowLike Share It is neither affiliated with nor endorsed by Twitter, Facebook, MySpace, Diigo, Reddit, StumbleUpon, Google, YouTube, Pinterest, Delicious, Reverbnation, Soundcloud, Tumblr, Linkedin, Vimeo, Fark, Bloggers, Friendfeed, Chime, Dzone, Buzzfeed, Clipboard or any other Social Network or Bookmarking Site.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at 

**PayPal Purchases**

PayPal transactions are subject to the PayPal Privacy Policy.

**Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you suspect usage of our services by someone under 13 you can report this to us using contact information below

**Changes to this privacy policy**

FollowLike has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Refund Policy**

Because coins are intangible goods, we cannot refund any purchase, so all coins bought can NOT be refunded. In the case of you having purchased more than the service we can deliver, we will process partial refund of the difference. Coins, Premium and Subscriptions are applied instantly but in some circumstances please allow up to 24 Hours. If 24 hours have passed contact us 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and 

terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy or terms, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

This document was last updated on May 24th, 2018
